Speaker 1: This photo is a remake of a popular painting by Grant Wood called American Gothic.
In the photo, two people are standing on the balcony of a flat,
or perhaps on the roof of a building.
On the right of the photo, there’s a man.
He’s probably about 30.
He’s wearing jeans, an orange top, and black boots.
He’s holding a garden fork in his hand.
Next to him, there’s a woman.
She’s a bit younger, about 25.
She’s probably his girlfriend, or maybe his wife, because they’re holding hands.
She has wavy brown hair.
It’s medium length, not long, but not really short.
She’s wearing a light blue hoodie, jeans, and boots.
She’s also wearing a bag round her waist.
In her hand, she’s holding a watering can.
The couple look happy.
They’re both smiling.
In the front of the photo, there are some pink flowers and some other green plants.
In the background, you can see the city, with many big modern buildings.
Perhaps they’re offices, or flats.
This is the original painting.
It was painted in 1930,
and it shows an old farmer and his daughter in front of their house.